[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What advice do the three mice from the pet shop in G-Force give to Blaster when a boy takes him from his cage?", "correct_answer": "Poop on his hand! Poop on his hand!", "incorrect_answers": ["Spit on his hand! Spit on his hand!", "Kiss him on the lips! Kiss him on the lips!", "Bite his hand! Bite his hand!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of ammo did the pulse rifles fire when used by the soldiers in the movie Aliens?", "correct_answer": "10 mm tip caseless", "incorrect_answers": ["knives and sharp sticks", "7.52 full metal jacket", "big ones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "We get the word boycott  from the name of Charles C. Boycott, a terrible  landlord of the 19th Century. Where did he own land?", "correct_answer": "Ireland", "incorrect_answers": ["England", "Scotland", "Massachusetts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the fictional planet that Anakin and Obi-Wan battle each other on?", "correct_answer": "Mustafar", "incorrect_answers": ["Geonosis", "Hoth", "Nemondia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is NOT one of cactis mechanisms for preserving water?", "correct_answer": "Reduced stem volume", "incorrect_answers": ["A waxy coating on the surface of the plant", "Reduced surface area", "Thick, hard-walled stem"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not among the tattoos the main character of Memento has on his body?", "correct_answer": "I loved her very much", "incorrect_answers": ["find him and kill him", "\u201cJohn G. Raped and Murdered My Wife.\u201d", "Ive done it"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who stars as Chris Gardner in the movie The Pursuit of Happyness?", "correct_answer": "Will Smith", "incorrect_answers": ["Tim Robbins", "Chris Gardner", "Samuel L. Jackson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many episodes of The Magnificent Seven series were made?", "correct_answer": "23", "incorrect_answers": ["20", "30", "25"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What celebrated supermodel did Richard Gere marry in 1991?", "correct_answer": "Cindy Crawford", "incorrect_answers": ["Elle Macpherson", "Christy Turlington", "Christie Brinkley"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the abbreviation THEL stand for?", "correct_answer": "Tactical high energy laser", "incorrect_answers": ["Thermabaric harmonic emergent light", "Thermobaric high energy light", "Titanium harmonic emergent laser"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest planet in the solar system?", "correct_answer": "Jupiter", "incorrect_answers": ["Neptune", "Mars", "Venus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the submarine guiding system, featured in the film For Your Eyes Only?", "correct_answer": "ATAC", "incorrect_answers": ["AVAS", "ALAP", "AZAG"]}]